Neugass, Fritz; Papers ger007
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Art market, art auctions, 1950-1979; 3; 217 folders
  - Art Prices of individual works, Undated (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 2)
    2 short articles, as well as numerous short texts in English.
  - Art as an Investment, Undated (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 3)
    Typescripts, including 2 book reviews (9), clippings.
  - Art as an Investment, Undated; Clippings (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 4)
  - Art Market, Legal and Tax Problems, Undated (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 5)
    Also fees of the auction houses.
    Typescripts (13), clippings.
  - Changes in the American Art Market during the last 20 years, Undated (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 6)
    Typescript, numerous notes and drafts.
  - Annual reports and reviews by Fritz Neugass, 1959-1979 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 7)
    Typescripts (18), copies of Franz Pick's World Currency Report, clippings.
  - Art Market in Europe, mainly of the 1960s (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 8)
  - World Art Market Conferences, 1976-1977 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 9)
    Contains texts by Fritz Neugass and others, publicity, clippings.
  - Book reviews of books on the art market, including 2 prefaces to Art Price Annual, Undated (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 10)
    Typescripts (6).
  - American Art auctions, Undated (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 11)
    Typescripts (5).
  - Parke-Bernet and Sotheby Merger, 1964 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 12)
    Photographs (4), typescripts (6), clippings.
  - Parke-Bernet Auction Reports, Undated (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 13)
    Typescripts (4).
  - Parke-Bernet Auctions, 3.14 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions))
    Listed chronologically by Sale Catalog No. and date.
    - Sale No. 1778 -- Georges Lurcy Collection, 1957 November 07-1957 November 09 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 14)
    - Sale No. 1857, 1958 November 19 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 15)
      Arnold Kirkeby Collection. Typescripts (2), clipping.
    - Sale No. 1867 -- Felix Kramarsky Collection, 1959 January 07-1959 January 10 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 16)
      Typescript, clipping.
    - Sale No. 1897, 1959 April 15; Typescript, clipping. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 17)
    - Sale No. 1905-1906, 1959 May 13; 1959 May 15-1959 May 16; 1959 May 22-1959 May 23 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 18)
      Thelma Chrysler Foy. Typescripts (2), clippings.
    - Sale No. 1959 -- Baroness Eva Gebhard Gourgaud, 1960 March 16; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 19)
    - Sale No. 2104 -- Old Masters, 1960 April 18; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 20)
    - Museum of Modern Art 30th Anniversary Fund Auction, 1960 April 27 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 21)
    - Sale No. 1989, 1992 -- Lillian S. Timkin, Gladys Lloyd Robinson, 1960 October 19; 1960 October 26; typescript (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 22)
    - Sale No. 1995, 1996. Myron C. Taylor, 1960 November 03-1960 November 05; 1960 November 11-1960 November 12 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 23)
    - Sale No. 2005 -- Modern Graphic Arts, 1960 December 14; typescript (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 24)
    - Sale No. 2013 -- Barbara Church, 1961 January 25; typescript (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 25)
    - Sale No. 2038 -- Primitives, Old Masters, XIX Century Paintings, 1961 May 10; typescript (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 26)
    - Sale No. 2040, 1961 May 16-1961 May 17 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 27)
      Oscar B. Cintas. Notes.
    - Sale No. 2056 -- Adolphe A. Juviler, 1961 October 25; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 28)
    - Sale No. 2062, 1961 November 15 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 29)
      Anna Erickson Sale of Old Master Paintings. Typescripts (6), notes, photographs (12), publicity, clippings.
    - Sale No. 2072 -- Modern Paintings, Drawings, Bronzes, 1961 December 13 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 30)
      Typescript, notes.
    - Sale No. 2076 -- Modern European & American Paintings, Drawings, Sculpture, 1962 January 11; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 31)
    - Sale No. 2096 -- Mr. & Mrs. Charles Goldman, 1962 March 21; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 32)
    - Sale No. 2101 -- Germaine Montabert, 1962 April 10 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 33)
    - Sale No. 2102 -- American Federation of Arts, 1962 April 11; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 34)
    - Sale No. 2114 -- America-Israel Cultural Foundation, 1962 May 16 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 35)
    - Sale No. 2122 -- Julia A. Berwind, The Elms, 1962 June 27-1962 June 28 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 36)
    - Sale No. 2132 -- Burlington Trust, 1962 October 17; typescript (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 37)
    - Sale No. 2135, 1962 October 24 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 38)
      John & Johanna Bass. Typescripts (2), clipping.
    - Sale No. 2140, 1962 November 08 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 39)
      Incunabula, Americana. Typescripts (2).
    - Sale No. 2142 -- May Bonfils Stanton, 1962 November 14 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 40)
    - Sale No. 2144 -- Miami Museum of Modern Art, 1962 November 24; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 41)
    - Sale No. 2146 -- Old Masters, 1962 November 28; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 42)
    - Sale No. 2158 -- Edward A. Gould, Kirk Douglas, 1963 January 24; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 43)
    - Sale No. 2171 -- Lester H. Dana, 1963 February 27; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 44)
    - Sale No. 2175 -- Old Masters Prints, 1963 March 14; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 45)
    - Sale No. 2183 -- William Randolph Hearst, 1963 April 05-1963 April 06; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 46)
    - Sale No. 2193 -- Oscar B. Cintas, 1963 May 01; Typescript, clipping. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 47)
    - Sale No. 2195, 1963 May 07-1963 May 08 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 48)
      Barton W. Currie Library. Notes, clipping.
    - Sale No. 2199 -- Nanette Fabray, 1963 May 15; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 49)
    - Sale No. 2211 -- American Paintings, 1963 October 09; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 50)
    - Sale No. 2220, 1963 October 30 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 51)
      Larry Aldrich. Typescripts (2), clipping.
    - Sale No. 2223 -- Barbizon, Edmund S. Burke Jr., 1963 November 06 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 52)
    - Sale No. 2240, 1963 December 11 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 53)
      Modern Paintings. Typescripts (2).
    - Sale No. 2264 -- Judaica, 1964 March 18-1964 March 19; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 54)
    - Sale No. 2270 -- Baron Elie de Rothschild, 1964 April 08 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 55)
      Typescript, notes, photograph.
    - Sale No. 2283 -- Abstract, 1964 May 13; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 56)
    - Sale No. 2300 -- Walter Ross, 1964 October 21 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 57)
      Typescript, photographs (13), clipping.
    - Sale No. 2311 -- Robert Q. Lewis, 1964 November 18 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 58)
      Typescript, photographs (8).
    - Sale No. 2321, 1965 January 13 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 59)
      Ira Haupt. Typescripts (3), clippings.
    - Sale No. 2326 -- American Paintings, 1965 January 27; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 60)
    - Sale No. 2344, 2345, 1965 April 14 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 61)
      Impressionist, Philippe Dotremont. Typescripts (3), notes, clippings.
    - Sale No. 2351 -- Mrs. A. Hamilton Rice, 1965 May 04-1965 May 05; Typescript, clipping. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 62)
    - Sale No. 2358 -- American Paintings, 1965 May 19; Typescript, clippings. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 63)
    - Sale No. 2369, 2371, Undated (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 64)
      Robert C. Skull, Impressionists. Typescripts (2), clippings.
    - Sale No. 2373, 1965 October 22-1965 October 23 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 65)
      Mrs. A. Hamilton Rice. Typescripts (2).
    - Sale No. 2391, 1965 December 08-1965 December 09 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 66)
      Impressionists. Typescripts (2), clippings.
    - Sale No. 2420, 1966 March 23-1966 March 24 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 67)
      G. David Thompson. Typescripts (3), notes, photographs (7), publicity, clippings.
    - Sale No. 2428-2432, 1966 April 20-1966 April 29 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 68)
      Helena Rubinstein. Typescripts (4), photographs (4), publicity, clippings.
    - Sale No. 2438, 1966 May 11 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 69)
      Whitney Museum of American Art Benefit. Typescripts (2).
    - Sale No. 2464 -- Charles Laughton, Eva Lanchester, 1966 October 20; Typescript, clipping. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 70)
    - Sale No. 2559 -- Primitive Art, 1967 May 04; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 71)
    - Sale No. 2570 -- Will Weissberg Photographic Collection, 1967 May 16 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 72)
    - Thomas W. Streeter Collection, 1966 October-1969 October (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 73)
    - Sale No. 2606, 1967 October 26 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 74)
      Impressionists. Typescripts (2).
    - Sale No. 2609 -- Nowell-Usticke Rembrandt Collection, 1967 October 31-1967 November 01; Typescript, clipping. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 75)
    - Sale No. 2677, 1968 April 03 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 76)
      Allan Bluestein. Typescripts (2), clipping.
    - Sale No. 2678 -- Elmer Rice Estate, 1968 April 04; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 77)
    - Sale No. 2696 -- Nowell-Usticke Rembrandt Collection, 1968 April 30-1968 May 01 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 78)
    - Sale No. 2741, 2742, 1968 October 09-10 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 79)
      Impressionist, Roudinesco school. Notes for an article, photograph, publicity, clippings.
    - Sale No. 2767 -- Impressionists, Modern, 1968 November 20; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 80)
    - Sale No. 2832 -- German Expressionists, 1969 April 09 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 81)
    - Auctions, 1969 April 15-1969 April 19; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 82)
    - Sale No. 2842 -- Melvin Gutman Jewelry, 1969 April 24 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 83)
    - Sale No. 2849, 1969 May 01 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 84)
      Russian Art. Photograph, publicity, clipping, no text.
    - Sale No. 2907, 1969 October 15 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 85)
      Grover A. & Jeanne J. Magnin Collection. Typescripts (2), photographs (4), publicity, clippings.
    - Sale No. 2914 -- American Paintings & Sculpture, 1969 October 22; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 86)
    - Sale No. 1931 -- Modern & Old Master Prints, 1969 November 12-1969 November 13; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 87)
    - Sale No. 2935 -- German Expressionists, 1969 November 19; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 88)
    - Sale No. 2994, 2996 -- Impressionists, Sculpture, 1970 February 25-1970 February 26 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 89)
    - Sale No. 2999 -- Harris B. Steinberg Collection, 1970 March 04 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 90)
    - Sale No. 3048 -- Impressionists, 1970 May 13 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 91)
      Typescript, notes, clipping.
    - Sale No. 3056, 1970 May 21 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 92)
      Charles Bird King Portraits. Photographs (2).
    - William Goetz. Photographs (2), clippings, 1970 October 14 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 93)
    - Sale No. 3096, 3097 -- Irma N. Strauss Collection, 1970 October 21-1970 October 22 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 94)
    - Sale No. 3102, 3104 -- Modern, 1970 October 28-1970 October 29; Typescript, clipping. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 95)
    - Sale No. 3113 -- German Expressionists, 1970 November 11; Typescript. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 96)
    - Sale No. 3118, 1970 November 18 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 97)
      Contemporary American. Typescripts (2), clippings.
    - Sale No. 3133 -- American Paintings, 1970 December 10; Typescript, clippings. (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 98)
    - Sale No. 3170 -- Impressionists, 1971 March 10 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 99)
      Typescript, notes, photograph, clippings.
    - Sale No. 3204, 1971 May 07-1971 May 08 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 100)
      Norton Simon Foundation. Typescripts (3), notes, photographs (8), publicity, clippings.
    - Sales of Graphic Art, 1971 June (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 101)
    - Sale No. 3247 -- Solomon R. Guggenheim Foundation, 1971 October 20 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 102)
    - Sale No. 3268 -- Post War & Contemporary Art, 1971 November 17 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 103)
    - Sale No. 3322, 1972 March 01 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 104)
      Sculpture. Typescripts (2).
    - Sale No. 3354, 1972 April 26-1972 April 27 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 105)
      Modern. Typescripts (2).
    - Sale No. 3360, 1972 May 02-1972 May 05 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 106)
      The Cranbrook Collections. Typescripts (2).
    - Sale No. 3370 -- Old Masters, 1972 May 17-1972 May 18 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 107)
    - Sale No. 3383 -- Mrs. E. F. Hutton, 1972 June 07-1972 June 10 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 108)
      Typescript, notes, publicity, clipping.
    - Sale No. 3409 -- Hans Popper Collection, Japanese Prints, 1972 October 05-1972 October 06 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 109)
    - Sale No. 3424 -- 19th & 20th Century Paintings, 1972 October 25 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 110)
    - Sale No. 3452 -- Deane Johnson Collection, 1972 December 09 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 111)
    - Sale No. 3474 -- Metropolitan Museum, 1973 February 15; typescript, clipping (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 112)
    - Sale No. 3484, 1973 March 15 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 113)
      Edith G. Halpert Collection. Typescripts (2), publicity, clippings.
    - 1973 March 17 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 114)
      Josef & Hadassah Rosensaft Collection. Photographs (2), publicity, clippings, no text.
    - Sale No. 3509, 3510, 1973 May 02-1973 May 04 (Box 14 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 115)
      Norton Simon Collection. Publicity, notes, clippings, no text.
  - Parke-Bernet Auctions, 3.15 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions))
    - Sale No. 3544, 1973 September 19; typescript (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 1)
    - Sale No. 3556A - C, 3557, 3559, 1973 October 17-1973 October 19 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 2)
      Robert C. Skull. Typescripts (5), photographs (5), publicity, clippings.
    - Sale No. 3565, 1973 November 01-1973 November 03 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 3)
      Medieval, Renaissance. Notes, clippings.
    - Sale No. 3630-3634, 1974 May 01-1974 May 04 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 4)
      Impressionists, Modern. Typescripts (4), photograph, clipping.
    - Sale No. 3674 -- 19th Century European Paintings, 1974 October 09 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 5)
      Typescripts (2).
    - Sale No. 3679, 3736 -- Chinese Works of Art, 1974 October 17-1974 October 18; 1975 March 12-1975 March 13; Typescript. (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 6)
    - Sale No. 3711 -- 19th Century European Paintings, 1975 January 16; Typescript. (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 7)
    - Sale No. 3728 -- Tapestries, Furniture, 1975 February 21 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 8)
    - Sale No. 3730, 1975 February 25 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 9)
      Photographs. Notes, clipping, no text.
    - Sale No. 3737, 1975 March 14 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 10)
      Lester Wolfe Collection of Persian Pottery. Notes, photographs (3), no text.
    - Sale No. 3753, 1975 May 02 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 11)
      Ray Winfield Smith Collection. Notes, publicity, no text.
    - Sale No. 3755 -- Old Master Paintings, 1975 May 06-1975 May 08 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 12)
      Notes, photographs (4), no text.
    - Sale No. 3761 - 3763, 1975 May 21-1975 May 22; typescript (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 13)
    - Sale No. 3784, 1975 September 23 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 14)
      19th & 20th Century Photographs. Draft, photograph.
    - Sale No. 3791, 1975 October 07-1975 October 11 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 15)
      Geraldine Rockefeller Dodge Estate. Typescripts (2), photographs (4), publicity, clippings.
    - Sale No. 3796-3798, 1975 October 22-1975 October 24; Typescript. (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 16)
    - Sale No. 3807 -- Prints, 1975 November 13-1975 November 14; Typescript. (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 17)
    - Sale No. 3816 -- Mrs. Charles E. Dunlap, 1975 December 03-1975 December 04; 1975 December 06; Typescript. (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 18)
    - Sale No. 3818 -- Geraldine Rockefeller Dodge Paintings, 1975 December 06; Typescript. (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 19)
    - Sale No. 3847, 1976 March 17 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 20)
      Josef Rosensaft. Typescripts (2).
    - Sale No. 3848 -- Lester Avnet, 1976 March 18 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 21)
    - Sale No. 3849 -- Chinese Art, 1976 March 20; Typescript. (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 22)
    - Sale No. 3867, 1976 May 04 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 23)
      Photographs. Publicity, photographs (2), clippings.
    - Sale No. 3868, 1976 May 05-1976 May 07 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 24)
      Prints. Notes, clippings, no text.
    - Sale No. 3870 -- Antiquities, Islamic Art, 1976 May 08; Typescript. (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 25)
    - Sale No. 3880-3883, 1976 May 26-1976 May 28 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 26)
      Typescripts (2), photograph, publicity, clipping.
    - Sale No. 3891 -- Old Masters, 1976 June 16-1976 June 17; Typescript. (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 27)
    - Sale No. 3980, 1977 April 28 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 28)
      19th Century European Paintings. Notes, no text.
    - Sale No. 3988, 1977 May 12-1977 May 13 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 29)
      Contemporary Art. Photograph, no text.
    - Sale No. 3992, 1977 May 18-1977 May 19 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 30)
      Prints. Photograph, no text.
    - Sale No. 3997, 1977 May 26 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 31)
      Mexican Art. Photograph, publicity, no text.
    - Sale No. 4030A, B, 1977 October 19 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 32)
      Sidney F. Brody, Impressionists. Photograph, publicity, clippings, no text.
    - Sale No. 4031, 1977 October 20 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 33)
      19th & 20th Century Drawings, Watercolors. Notes, no text.
    - Sale No. 4032, 1977 October 20 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 34)
      Contemporary. Photographs (2), publicity.
    - Sale No. 4068 -- Old Masters, 1978 January 13 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 35)
      Draft, publicity, clippings.
    - Sale No. 4098 -- John J. McDonough Collection, 1978 March 22 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 36)
      Typescript, draft, notes, photographs (3), publicity, clippings.
    - Sale No. 4122 -- 19th Century European Paintings, 1978 May 12 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 37)
      Typescript, draft, notes.
    - Sale No. 4126, 1978 May 18 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 38)
      Pop Art. Publicity, photograph, no text.
    - Sale No. 229 (SPB, Los Angeles), 1978 June 05-1978 June 08 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 39)
    - 1978 June 20-1978 June 23, 1978 June 26-1978 June 27 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 40)
      Robert von Hirsch Collection. Publicity, numerous clippings, no text.
    - Sale No. 4171, 1978 November 02 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 41)
      Contemporary Art. Notes, publicity, no text.
    - Sale No. 4172, 1978 November 03 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 42)
      Russian & European Avant-Garde. Notes, publicity, no text.
    - Sale No. 4196 -- Antiquities, 1978 December 14 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 43)
      Typescript, proofs, photograph, publicity, clippings.
    - Sale No. 4243, 1979 May 08 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 44)
      Photographs. Publicity, photographs (4), no text.
    - Sale No. 4247, 1979 May 16 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 45)
      German Expressionists. Notes, no text, photographs (2), publicity.
    - Sale No. 4260, 1979 June 05-1979 June 09 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 46)
      Benjamin Sonnenberg Collection. Photograph, publicity, clippings, no text.
    - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Auction publicity, 1938-1979 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 47-48)
      Some clippings.
    - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Auctions, Undated; Clippings (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 49)
    - Photographs (14) of items sold at Christie's Auctions, 1960-1961 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 50)
    - Christie's Sale of Captain Edward George Spencer - Churchill Collection, 1965 April (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 51)
    - Photographs (9) of items sold at Christie's Auctions, 1965 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 52)
    - Christie's 200-year Jubilee Sale, 1967 January 02-1967 January 20 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 53)
      See also Box 25, Folder 12.
    - (Christie's Auction), 1977 May 26 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 54)
      Photograph, no text.
    - Christie's advertisements, 1977 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 55)
    - (Christie's Auction), 1978 May 19-1978 May 20 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 56)
      Notes, photographs (2), no text.
    - Gutenberg Bible Auction at Christie's, 1978 April 07 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 57)
      Typescripts (5), notes, photographs (2), publicity, clippings.
    - (Christie's Auction), 1978 October 27 (Box 15 (3-Art market, art auctions), Folder 58)
      Typescripts (2), notes, photograph, publicity, clippings.